Robert Houghwout Jackson Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Legal File, 1919-1962 (Box 59-188)
  - Supreme Court (Box 119)
    - October term 1946
      - Cases
        - United States v. United Mine Workers; United Mine Workers v. United States, Nos. 759-760, 781, and 811; (2 folders) (Box 140)
        - United States v. Munsey Trust Co., No. 847
    - October term 1947
      - Chief justice
      - Law clerks
      - Miscellaneous correspondence and papers
      - Cases
        - Winters v. New York (continuation of case No. 33, October term 1946), No. 3
        - United States v. John J. Felin & Co., No. 17 (Box 141)
        - Sherrer v. Sherrer, No. 36
        - Coe v. Coe (continuation of case No. 958, October term 1946), No. 37
        - Maggio v. Zeitz, No. 38; (3 folders)
        - Oyama v. California (continuation of case No. 1059, October term 1946), No. 44 (Box 142)
        - Federal Crop Ins. Corp. v. Merrill, No. 45
        - International Salt Co. v. United States, No. 46
        - Shapiro v. United States, No. 49; (2 folders)
        - Musser v. Utah, No. 60
        - United States v. Di Re, No. 61
        - Panhandle E. Pipe Line Co. v. Public Serv. Comm'n, No. 69 (Box 143)
        - Shelley v. Kraemer; McGhee v. Sipes; Hurd v. Hodge; Urciolo v. Hodge (restrictive covenant cases), Nos. 72, 87, 290, and 291
        - von Moltke v. Gillies, No. 73
        - Mandeville Island Farms v. American Crystal Sugar Co., No. 75
        - Chicago & S. Air Lines v. Waterman S.S. Corp.; Civil Aeronautics Bd. v. Waterman S.S. Corp., Nos. 78 and 88
        - Illinois ex rel. McCollum v. Board of Educ. of School Dist. No. 71, Champaign County, Ill., No. 90; (2 folders)
        - Lee v. Mississippi, No. 91 (Box 144)
        - Price v. Johnston, No. 111
        - Capitol Greyhound Lines v. Brice, No. 118
        - Estin v. Estin, No. 139
        - Massachusetts v. United States, No. 157
        - United States v. South Buffalo Ry., No. 198
        - In re Oliver, No. 215
        - Commissioner v. Sunnen, No. 227
        - Schwabacher v. United States, No. 258; (2 folders) (Box 145)
        - Fisher v. Hurst See also same container, No. 369, No. 325 Misc.
        - Johnson v. United States, No. 329
        - Callen v. Pennsylvania R.R., No. 331
        - Connecticut Mut. Life Ins. Co. v. Moore, No. 337
        - Sipuel v. Board of Regents of the Univ. of Okla. See also same container, No. 325 Misc., No. 369
        - Kreiger v. Kreiger, No. 371
        - Bob-Lo Excursion Co. v. Michigan, No. 374
        - Woods v. Stone, No. 392 (Box 146)
        - Toomer v. Witsell, No. 415
        - Tripiana v. United States, No. 427
        - Parker v. Illinois, No. 428
        - Ahrens v. Clark, No. 446
        - Comstock v. Group of Institutional Investors; New Orleans, Tex. & Mex. Ry. v. Group of Institutional Investors; Thompson v. Group of Institutional Investors; Comstock v. Thompson, Nos. 451-454
        - Federal Trade Comm'n v. Morton Salt Co., No. 464
        - Moore v. New York, No. 485
        - Woods v. The Cloyd W. Miller Co., No. 486
        - Saia v. New York, No. 504 (Box 147)
        - Briggs v. Pennsylvania R.R., No. 530
        - Takahashi v. Fish & Game Comm'n, No. 533
        - Gryger v. Burke, No. 541
        - Townsend v. Burke, No. 542
        - United States v. National City Lines, No. 544
        - Kennedy v. Silas Mason Co., No. 590
        - Hunter v. Martin, No. 643
        - United States v. Congress of Indus. Orgs., No. 695
        - Ludecke v. Watkins, No. 723
    - October term 1948 (Box 148)
      - Chief justice
      - Miscellaneous correspondence
      - Cases
        - Estate of Spiegal v. Commissioner; Commissioner v. Estate of Church (continuation of case no. 52, October term 1947), Nos. 3 and 5; (2 folders)
        - Grand River Dam Auth. v. Grand-Hydro, No. 6
        - Jungersen v. Ostby & Barton Co.; Ostby & Barton Co. v. Jungersen; Jungersen v. Baden, Nos. 7-8 and 48
        - Kovacs v. Cooper, No. 9
        - Brinegar v. United States, No. 12; (2 folders) (Box 149)
        - United States v. Urbeteit, No. 13
        - United Auto. Workers Local 232 v. Wisconsin Employment Relations Bd., Nos. 14-15; (2 folders)
        - Vermilyn-Brown Co. v. Connell, No. 22; (1 folder) (Box 150)
        - Michelson v. United States, No. 23
        - Hynes v. Grimes Packing Co., No. 24
        - Eckenrode v. Pennsylvania R.R., No. 28
        - National Mut. Ins. Co. v. Tidewater Transfer Co., No. 29; (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 151)
        - Larson v. Domestic & Foreign Commerce Corp., No. 31; (2 folders)
        - McDonald v. United States, No. 36
        - United States v. Women's Sportswear Mfrs. Ass'n, No. 37 (Box 152)
        - Oklahoma Tax Comm'n v. The Texas Co.; Oklahoma Tax Comm'n v. Magnolia Petroleum Co., Nos. 40-41
        - Klapprott v. United States, No. 42
        - Frazier v. United States (continuation of case No. 213 Misc., October term 1947), No. 44
        - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Stowe Spinning Co., No. 46
        - Railway Express Agency v. New York, No. 51
        - Wilkerson v. McCarthy, No. 53
        - Marzani v. United States, No. 59
        - Harris v. South Carolina (continuation of case No. 503 Misc., October term 1947) See also Containers 153, No. 107, and 157, No. 610, No. 76
        - Commissioner v. Wodehouse, No. 84 (Box 153)
        - Leiman v. Guttman, No. 88
        - Henslee v. Union Planters Nat'l Bank & Trust Co., No. 90
        - H. P. Hood & Sons v. Du Mond, No. 92; (2 folders)
        - Turner v. Pennsylvania (continuation of case No. 567 Misc., October term 1947) See also Containers 152, No. 76, and 157, No. 610, No. 107
        - Federal Power Comm'n v. Interstate Natural Gas Co.; Public Serv. Comm'n v. Interstate Natural Gas Co.; Memphis Light Gas & Water Div. v. Interstate Natural Gas Co.; Illinois Commerce Comm'n v. Interstate Natural Gas Co., Nos. 109, 188, 209, and 212
        - McComb v. Jacksonville Paper Co., No. 110
        - Rice v. Rice, No. 117 (Box 154)
        - Black Diamond S.S. Corp. v. Robert Stewart & Sons; United States v. Robert Stewart & Sons, Nos. 121 and 130
        - Farmers Reservoir & Irrigation Co. v. McComb; McComb v. Farmers Reservoir & Irrigation Co., Nos. 128 and 196
        - Krulewitch v. United States, No. 143
        - German cases, Nos. 156, 234, 249, and 259 Misc.
        - City of New York v. Saper; New York v. Carter; United States v. Carter, Nos. 168 and 200-201
        - Giboney v. Empire Storage & Ice Co., No. 182 (Box 155)
        - Murphey v. Reed, No. 206
        - Nye & Nissen v. United States, No. 228
        - Hirota v. MacArthur; Dohihara v. MacArthur; Kido v. MacArthur, Nos. 239-240 Misc. and 248 Misc.
        - Ott v. Mississippi Valley Barge Line Co., No. 244
        - Eisler v. United States, No. 255
        - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Pittsburgh S.S. Co., No. 258
        - Farrell v. United States, No. 267
        - Terminiello v. City of Chicago, No. 272; (1 folder) (Box 156)
        - Standard Oil Co. v. United States, No. 279
        - Commissioner v. Culbertson, No. 313
        - California v. Zook, No. 355
        - Transcontinental & W. Air v. Civil Aeronautics Bd., No. 387
        - Propper v. Clark, No. 390 (Box 157)
        - Cohen v. Beneficial Indus. Loan Corp.; Beneficial Indus. Loan Corp. v. Smith, Nos. 442 and 512
        - Wheeling Steel Corp. v. Glander; National Distillers Prods. Corp. v. Glander, Nos. 447-448
        - Woods v. Interstate Realty Co., No. 465
        - Christoffel v. United States, No. 528
        - Watts v. Indiana See also Containers 152, No. 76, and 153, No. 107, No. 610
        - Johnson v. Stevenson (Texas cases), No. --
    - October term 1949
      - Applications, hearings, bail, etc.
      - Chief justice
      - Law clerks
      - Miscellaneous correspondence and papers (Box 158)
      - Record of opinions circulated
      - Cases
        - United States v. Kansas City Life Ins. Co., No. l
        - Graver Tank & Mfg. Co. v. Linde Air Prods. Co. (continuation of case Nos. 184-l85, October term 1948), No. 2
        - United States v. Gerlach Live Stock Co.; United States v. Potter; United States v. Erreca; United States v. James J. Stevinson (A Corp.); United States v. Stevinson; United States v. 3-H Sec. Co., Nos. 4-9; (2 folders)
        - American Communications Ass'n v. Douds; United Steelworkers v. National Labor Relations Bd., Nos. 10 and 13; (3 folders) (Box 159)
        - Osman v. Douds, No. 12
        - Dennis v. United States, No. 14
        - Graham v. Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen & Enginemen, No. 16
        - Boyd v. Grand Trunk W. R.R., No. 17
        - Standard-Vacuum Oil Co. v. United States, No. 18
        - United States v. Yellow Cab Co., No. 22 (Box 160)
        - Roth v. Delano, No. 24
        - Henderson v. United States, No. 25
        - United States v. Westinghouse Elec. & Mfg. Co., No. 26; (2 folders)
        - McLaurin v. Oklahoma State Regents for Higher Educ., No. 34
        - United States v. Spelar, No. 42
        - United States v. Benedict, No. 45
        - Cassell v. Texas, No. 46; (1 folder) (Box 161)
        - Parker v. County of Los Angeles; Steiner v. County of Los Angeles, Nos. 49-50
        - Darr v. Burford, No. 51
        - Kingsland v. Dorsey, No. 53
        - United States ex. rel. Knauff v. Shaughnessy See also Container 164, No. -- United States ex rel. Knauff v. McGrath, No. 54
        - O'Donnell v. Elgin, Joliet & E. Ry., No. 56
        - Chapman v. Sheridan-Wyoming Coal Co., No. 60
        - Cole v. Arkansas, No. 62
        - Federal Power Comm'n v. East Ohio Gas Co., No. 71; (2 folders) (Box 162)
        - United States v. Moorman, No. 97
        - United States v. Bryan, No. 99; (2 folders)
        - United States v. Pacific Wholesalers' Ass'n; Freight Forwarders Inst. v. Pacific Wholesalers' Ass'n, Nos. 113-114
        - Dickinson v. Petroleum Conversion Corp., No. 150
        - Wong Yang Sung v. McGrath, No. 154 (Box 163)
        - United States v. Commodities Trading Corp.; Commodities Trading Corp. v. United States, Nos. 156 and 163
        - Aff*older v. New York, Chicago & St. Louis R.R., No. 200
        - United States v. Alpers, No. 217
        - United States v. Morton Salt Co.; United States v. International Salt Co., Nos. 273-274
        - United States v. Rabinowitz, No. 293
        - Johnson v. Eisentrager, No. 306; (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 164)
        - International Bhd. of Teamsters Local 309 v. Hanke; Automobile Drivers & Demonstrators Local 882 v. Cline, Nos. 309 and 364
        - Railway Labor Executives' Ass'n v. United States, No. 337
        - Mullane v. Central Hanover Bank & Trust Co., No. 378
        - United States v. National Ass'n of Real Estate Bds., No. 428
        - Lyon v. Singer; Singer v. Yokohama Specie Bank; Lyon v. Banque Mellie Iran; Banque Mellie Iran v. Lyon, Nos. 512-513 and 527-528
        - Ewing v. Mytinger & Casselberry, No. 568
        - South v. Peters, No. 724
        - United States ex rel. Knauff v. McGrath See also Container 161, No. 54, No. --
    - October term 1950 (Box 165)
      - Applications, hearings, bail, etc. (Williamson v. United States, application for bail)
      - Chief justice
      - Law clerks
      - Miscellaneous correspondence and papers
      - Record of opinions circulated
      - Cases
        - Standard Oil Co. v. Federal Trade Comm'n, No. 1
        - National Council of Am. Soviet Friendship v. McGrath, No. 7
        - Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee Comm. v. McGrath; National Council of Am. Soviet Friendship v. McGrath; International Workers Order v. McGrath, Nos. 7-8 and 71; (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 166)
        - Feres v. United States; Jefferson v. United States; United States v. Griggs, Nos. 9, 29, and 31
        - United States v. Security Trust & Sav. Bank of San Diego, Nos. 10-13
        - Harris v. Commissioner, No. 14
        - Missouri ex rel. Southern Ry. v. Mayfield; Missouri ex rel. Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Ry. v. Murphy, Nos. 15-16
        - Niemotko v. Maryland; Kelley v. Maryland, Nos. 17-18
        - Rogers v. United States; Blau v. United States, Nos. 20-21
        - Blau v. United States, No. 22
        - United States v. Williams, No. 26
        - Great Britain & Pac. Tea Co. v. Supermarket Equip. Corp., No. 32
        - McGrath v. Kristensen, No. 34 (Box 167)
        - Bailey v. Richardson, No. 49
        - Kunz v. New York, No. 50
        - Montana-Dakota Utils. Co. v. Northwestern Pub. Serv. Co., No. 77
        - Warren v. United States, No. 87
        - Feiner v. New York, No. 93
        - Canton R.R. v. Rogan; Western Md. Ry. Co. v. Rogan, Nos. 96 and 205
        - Norton Co. v. Department of Revenue, No. 133
        - West Virginia ex rel. Dyer v. Sims, No. 147
        - Sacher v. United States, No. 201; (2 folders) (Box 168)
        - Collins v. Hardyman, No. 217
        - Zittman v. McGrath; McCarthy v. McGrath; McCloskey v. McGrath, Nos. 298-299, 314-315, and 324
        - Dennis v. United States, No. 336; (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 169)
        - Jordan v. De George, No. 348; (2 folders)
        - Timken Roller Bearing Co. v. United States, No. 352
        - Land v. Dollar; In re Killion; Sawyer v. Dollar, Nos. 353, 697, 702, — and— (Box 170)
        - Williams v. United States, No. 365
        - Shepherd v. Florida, No. 420
        - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Highland Park Mfg. Co., No. 425
        - Schwegmann Bros. v. Calvert Distillers Corp.; Schwegmann Bros. v. Seagram Distillers Corp., Nos. 442-443
        - Garner v. Board of Pub. Works, No. 453
        - Mooser v. Darrow, No. 461
        - Panhandle E. Pipe Line Co. v. Michigan Pub. Serv. Comm'n, No. 486
        - Pohl v. Acheson, No. 643
    - October term 1951 (Box 171)
      - Applications, hearing, bail, etc.
      - Chief justice
      - Law clerks
      - Miscellaneous correspondence and papers
      - Record of opinions circulated
      - Cases
        - Georgia R.R. & Banking Co. v. Redwine, No. 1
        - Adler v. Board of Educ., No. 8
        - Doremus v. Board of Educ., No. 9
        - United States v. Wunderlich, No. 11
        - Morissette v. United States, No. 12; (2 folders)
        - McMahon v. United States, No. 17 (Box 172)
        - United States v. Oregon State Medical Soc'y, No. 19
        - Carlson v. Landon; Butterfield v. Zydok, Nos. 35 and 136
        - Palmer v. Ashe, No. 38
        - Harisiades v. Shaughnessy; Mascitti v. McGrath; Coleman v. McGrath, Nos. 43, 206, and 264; (2 folders)
        - United States v. Jordan; United States v. Shannon, Nos. 46-47 (Box 173)
        - Rochin v. California, No. 83
        - Gallegos v. Nebraska, No. 94
        - Jennings v. Illinois; La Frana v. Illinois; Sherman v. Illinois, Nos. 95-96 and 375
        - Beauharnais v. Illinois, No. 118
        - Gray v. Board of Trustees of the Univ. of Tenn.; Ex parte Gray, Nos. 129 and 159 Misc.
        - Sutton v. Leib, No. 143
        - Muth v. Aetna Oil Co., No. 147
        - United States v. Great N. Ry., No. 151
        - Florida R.R. & Pub. Utils. Comm'n v. Atlantic Coast Line R. Co., No. 159
        - Buck v. California, No. 165
        - Boyce Motor Lines v. United States, No. 167 (Box 174)
        - Kaufman v. Societe Int'l Pour Participations Indus. et Commerciales, No. 172
        - Lykes v. United States, No. 173
        - Leland v. Oregon, No. 176
        - Kerotest Mfg. Co. v. C-O-Two Fire Equip. Co., No. 180
        - Koehler v. United States, No. 199
        - Public Utils. Comm'n v. Pollak; Pollak v. Public Utils. Comm'n, Nos. 224 and 295
        - Besser Mfg. Co. v. United States, No. 230
        - Desper v. Starved Rock Ferry Co., No. 231
        - Day-Brite Lighting v. Missouri, No. 317
        - First Nat'l Bank of Chicago v. United Air Lines, No. 349
        - Dice v. Akron, Canton & Youngstown R.R., No. 374
        - Stack v. Boyle, No. 400
        - United States v. Hood, No. 426
        - Zorach v. Clauson, No. 431 (Box 175)
        - United States v. Spector, No. 443
        - Federal Trade Comm'n v. Ruberoid Co.; Ruberoid Co. v. Federal Trade Comm'n, Nos. 448 and 504
        - Joseph Burstyn, Inc. v. Wilson, No. 522
        - Lee v. United States, No. 543
        - Kawakita v. United States, No. 570
        - Ray v. Blair, No. 649 (Box 176)
        - Youngstown Sheet & Tube Co. v. Sawyer; Sawyer v. Youngstown Sheet & Tube Co., Nos. 744-745; (4 folders)
    - October term 1952 (Box 177)
      - Applications, hearing, bail, etc.
      - Chief justice
      - Law clerks
      - Miscellaneous correspondence and papers
      - Record of opinions circulated
      - Cases
        - Kedroff v. Saint Nicholas Cathedral, No. 3; (2 folders)
        - Dixon v. Duffy See also Container 120, Opinion notes, Habeas corpus, No. 4
        - Sawyer v. Dollar, No. 5
        - New Jersey v. New York, No. 5 Orig.
        - Texas v. New Mexico, No. 9 Orig.
        - United States v. Henning, No. 10
        - United States v. Bell Aircraft Corp., No. 13
        - Mandoli v. Acheson, No. 15 (Box 178)
        - United States v. L. A. Tucker Truck Lines, No. 18
        - United States v. Reynolds, No. 21
        - Brown v. Allen; Speller v. Allen; Daniels v. Allen; United States ex rel. Smith v. Baldi See also Container 120, Opinion notes, Habeas corpus, Nos. 32, 22, 20, and 31; (3 folders)
        - Nathanson v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 33 (Box 179)
        - Brock v. North Carolina, No. 34
        - Steele v. Bulova Watch Co., No. 38
        - Baumet v. United States, No. 39
        - F. W. Woolworth Co. v. Contemporary Arts, Inc., No. 42
        - Public Serv. Comm'n v. Wycoff Co., No. 44
        - United States v. Universal C.I.T. Credit Corp., No. 47
        - Arrowsmith v. Commissioner, No. 51
        - Terry v. Adams, No. 52
        - Pennsylvania R.R. v. O'Rourke, No. 60
        - Lutwak v. United States, No. 66
        - Edelman v. California, No. 85
        - Shaughnessy v. United States ex rel. Mezei, No. 139 (Box 180)
        - Western Pac. R.R. v. Western Pac. R.R.; Metzger v. Western Pac. R.R., Nos. 150 and 160
        - United States v. Kahriger, No. 167
        - Gordon v. United States, No. 182
        - Bode v. Barrett; Coordinated Transp. v. Barrett, Nos. 187 and 274
        - City of New York v. New York, New Haven & Hartford R.R., No. 203
        - United States v. Public Utils. Comm'n; County of Mineral Nevada v. Public Utils. Comm'n, Nos. 205-206
        - Lauritzen v. Larsen, No. 226
        - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Gamble Enters., No. 238 (Box 181)
        - May v. Anderson, No. 244
        - Baltimore & Ohio R.R. v. United States, No. 258
        - Calmar S.S. Corp. v. United States, No. 262
        - Polizzi v. Cowles Magazines, No. 287
        - Howard v. Commissioners of the Sinking Fund of the City of Louisville, No. 295
        - Calmar S.S. v. Scott, No. 303
        - Dalehite v. United States, No. 308; (2 folders)
        - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Rockaway News Supply Co., No. 318
        - Fowler v. Rhode Island, No. 340
        - Poulos v. New Hampshire, No. 341 (Box 182)
        - Christoffel v. United States, No. 341 Misc.
        - Times-Picayune Publishing Co. v. United States; United States v. Times-Picayune Publishing Co., Nos. 374-375
        - Stein v. New York; Wissner v. New York; Cooper v. New York, Nos. 391-393; (3 folders)
        - Wells v. Simonds Abrasive Co., No. 394 (Box 183)
        - Orvis v. Brownell, No. 404
        - United States v. Carroll, No. 442
        - Orloff v. Willoughby, No. 444
        - District of Columbia v. John R. Thompson Co., No. 617
    - June 18 special term 1953
      - Cases
        - Rosenberg v. United States, (3 folders)
    - October term 1953 (Box 184)
      - Applications, hearings, bail, etc.
      - Law clerks
      - Miscellaneous correspondence and papers
      - Record of opinions circulated
      - Cases
        - Segregation cases
          - Brown v. Board of Educ., No. 1
          - Briggs v. Elliott (S.C.), No. 2
          - Davis v. County School Bd. of Prince Edward County, Va., No. 4
          - Gebhart v. Belton (Del.), No. 10
          - Bolling v. Sharpe, No. 8
          - Correspondence and press clippings
          - Jackson working papers (not circulated)
        - Watson v. Employers Liab. Assurance Co., No. 6 (Box 185)
        - Wilburn Boat Co. v. Fireman's Fund Ins. Co., No. 7
        - Arizona v. California (continued from October term 1952), No. 10 Orig.
        - Irvine v. California, No. 12
        - Pope & Talbot, Inc. v. Hawn, No. 13
        - United States v. Five Gambling Devices; United States v. Denmark; United States v. Braun, Nos. 14 and 40-41
        - Bankers Life & Casualty Co. v. Holland, No. 16
        - Toolson v. New York Yankees; Kowalski v. Chandler; Corbett v. Chandler, Nos. 18, 23, and 25
        - Voris v. Eikel, No. 20
        - United States v. Morgan, No. 31 (Box 186)
        - United States v. Harriss, No. 32
        - Howell Chevrolet Co. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 34
        - Wilko v. Swan, No. 39
        - Building Trades Council v. Kinard Constr. Co.; United Constr. Workers v. Laburnum Constr. Corp.; Capital Serv. v. National Labor Relations Bd., Nos. 48, 188, and 398
        - Pereira v. United States, No. 50
        - Garner v. Teamsters Local 776, No. 56
        - Dickinson v. United States, No. 57
        - Quinn v. United States, No. 66
        - Emspak v. United States, No. 67
        - Miller Bros. Co. v. Maryland, No. 160 (Box 187)
        - Railway Express Agency v. Virginia, No. 163
        - International Longshoremen's & Warehousesmen's Local 37 v. Boyd, No. 195
        - Michigan-Wisconsin Pipe Line Co. v. Calvert; Panhandle E. Pipe Line Co. v. Calvert, Nos. 198-201
        - Adams v. Maryland, No. 271
        - Sacher v. Association of the Bar of the City of New York, No. 307
        - United States ex rel. Accardi v. Shaughnessy, No. 366
        - Walters v. City of St. Louis, No. 389
        - Brownell v. Singer; Superintendent of Banks v. Singer, Nos. 401-402
        - Franklin Nat'l Bank v. New York, No. 427
        - Braniff Airways v. Nebraska State Bd. of Equalization & Assessment, No. 476 (Box 188)
        - In re Isserman (continuation of case No. 5, Misc., October term 1952), No. 513
        - Alton v. Alton, No. 531
        - Leyra v. Denno, No. 635
        - National Sur. Corp. v. McDowell See Container 185, No. 6, No. 716
        - Arkansas v. Texas, No.---Orig.
        - Rhode Island v. Louisiana, No.---Orig.
    - October term 1954
      - Applications, hearings, bail, etc.
      - Chief justice
      - Conference list, 4 Oct. 1954
      - Law clerks
  - Miscellany
- Biographical File, 1936-1970 (Box 188-191)
  Draft of autobiography, transcript of oral history interviews, drafts of chapters from published biographies, biographical sketches, and related correspondence.
  Arranged by title of publication or type of material.
  - America's Advocate: Robert H. Jackson, by Eugene C. Gerhart, 1958 (Box 188)
    - Chapters from early draft, (2 folders)
    - Related correspondence and book review, 1954-1961
  - Autobiography (Box 189)
    - Draft, (3 folders)
    - Outline, notes, and source material
  - Biographical sketches
    - 1936-1967, undated, (2 folders)
  - Biography, thesis by Robert C. Hubbard, May 1950
  - Biography of Jackson by Philip B. Kurland, 1969-1970
  - "A Decade of Mr. Justice Jackson," by Eugene C. Gerhart, New York University Law Review, May 1953 (Box 190)
  - "Justice Jackson's Story," transcript of tape recording taken by Harlan B. Phillips, Oral History Research Office, Columbia University, New York, N.Y., 1952-1953 See also Containers 258-259, Oral history transcript, (4 folders); (6 folders) (Box 191)
- Financial Papers, 1918-1954 (Box 192-201)